hamienet.com 2002-06-10

# HamieNet.com ::::: PRIVACY STATEMENT :::::

HamieNet.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: HamieNet.com. 

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and email address) and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). The customer's contact information is used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor the visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences.

This site contains links to other sites. **HamieNet.com** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

Our online surveys asks visitors for contact information (like their email address) and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). The customer's contact information is used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences.

## Public Forums

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

> This bulletin board will store a few details about you whilst you are using the bulletin board. The board administrator takes all reasonable steps to ensure that no unauthorised access to the information is granted. 
> 
> The following information is collected. 
> 
> **Cookies**
> 
> The bulletin board software will set the following cookies: 
> 
> Membername: This is so the board can 'remember' your username when using the bulletin board. This cookie is called 'amembernamecookie'. 
> 
> Password: This is so you don't have to re-tpye in your password everytime you wish to make a post or use any of the member only features on the board. This cookie is called 'apasswordcookie'. 
> 
> Last Visit Data: So that you can be made aware of any new posts since your last visit, two cookies are stored. One called 'templastvisit', the other 'lastvisit'. These only store data in a numerical format. 
> 
> **IP address**   
>  When you register and when you make a post - your IP address is stored on our server. This protects you as a member and us as a company when identifying that the user who posted is indeed authentic. This information will only be used if you misuse any features on the board or in any dispute. The board administrator is able to ban by IP address 
> 
> **Registration Form**   
>  The registration process is designed so that you can keep a unique identity. The only required parts to the registration process is the 'Membername' and 'Email address'. There is an option to keep this email address private if you wish. The bulletin board administrator will take all reasonable measures to ensure that any information you provide confidentially is kept confidential. You may change this information at any time by editing your profile. 
> 
> **Postings**   
>  The board administrator(s) cannot be held responsible for the content of posted messages on the forums. 

## Supplementation Information

This site supplements the information that you provide with information that is received from third parties.

## Children's Guidelines

  1. NOT collect online contact information without prior parental consent or parental notification, which will include an opportunity for the parent to prevent use of the information and participation in the activity. Without prior parental consent, online information will only be used to respond directly to the child's request and will not be used for other purposes without prior parental consent
  2. NOT collect personally identifiable offline contact information without prior parental consent
  3. NOT distribute to third parties any personally identifiable information with out prior parental consent
  4. NOT give the ability to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable contact information without prior parental consent
  5. NOT entice by the prospect of a special game, prize or other activity, to divulge more information than is needed to participate in the activity

## Choice/Opt-Out

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor.

This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. 

  1. You can post on [Forum](http://forum.hamienet.com/)

## Change/Modify

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. 

  1. Post on [Forum](http://forum.hamienet.com/)

## Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact 

Administration HamieNet.com
* Post on [Forum](http://forum.hamienet.com/)
